<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hyperledger Caliper</title>
    <link href="/2020/03/16/Hyperledger-Caliper/"/>
    <url>/2020/03/16/Hyperledger-Caliper/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Caliper-简介"><a href="#Caliper-简介" class="headerlink" title="Caliper 简介"></a>Caliper 简介</h2><p>Caliper是一个区块链性能基准框架，允许用户使用自定义用例测试不同的区块链解决方案，并获得一组性能测试结果。</p><blockquote><p>Caliper is a blockchain benchmark framework which allows users to measure the performance of a specific blockchain implementation with a set of predefined use cases. Caliper will produce reports containing a number of performance indicators, such as TPS (Transactions Per Second), transaction latency, resource utilisation etc. The intent is for Caliper results to be used as a reference in supporting the choice of a blockchain implementation suitable for the user-specific use-cases. Given the variety of blockchain configurations, network setup, as well as the specific use-cases in mind, it is not intended to be an authoritative performance assessment, nor to be used for simple comparative purposes (e.g. blockchain A does 5 TPS and blockchain B does 10 TPS, therefore B is better). The Caliper project references the definitions, metrics, and terminology as defined by the Performance &amp; Scalability Working Group (PSWG).</p></blockquote><h2 id="适用平台"><a href="#适用平台" class="headerlink" title="适用平台"></a>适用平台</h2><ul><li>Hyperledger Besu  </li><li>Hyperledger Burrow</li><li>Ethereum  </li><li>Hyperledger Fabric</li><li>FISCO BCOS</li><li>Hyperledger Iroha</li><li>Hyperledger Sawtooth</li><li>Transaction/read throughput</li><li>Transaction/read latency (minimum, maximum, average, percentile)</li><li>Resource consumption (CPU, Memory, Network IO, …)</li></ul><h2 id="安装Caliper"><a href="#安装Caliper" class="headerlink" title="安装Caliper"></a>安装Caliper</h2><p>Caliper is published as the <code>hyperledger/caliper-cli</code> NPM package and the <code>hyperledger/caliper</code><br> Docker image, both containing the CLI binary. Refer to the<br>Installing from NPM<br> and<br>Using the Docker image<br> sections for the available versions and their intricacies.</p><p>Installing and running Caliper usually consists of the following steps, thoroughly detailed by the remaining sections:</p><p>Acquire the Caliper CLI either from NPM or from DockerHub.<br>Execute a bind command through the CLI. This step pulls the specified version of SDK packages for the selected platform.<br>Start the benchmark through the CLI or by starting the Docker container.<br>The examples in the rest of the documentation use the<br>caliper-benchmarks<br> repository as the Caliper workspace since it contains many sample artifacts for benchmarking. Make sure you check out the appropriate tag/commit of the repository, matching the version of Caliper you use.</p><p>To clone the caliper-benchmarks repository, run:</p><pre><code>git clone https://github.com/hyperledger/caliper-benchmarks.gitcd caliper-benchmarksgit checkout &lt;your Caliper version&gt;</code></pre><p><em>Note</em>: If you are running your custom benchmark, then change this directory path (and other related configurations) accordingly in the examples.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>Hyperledger</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>区块链</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
